Guide to the Center for Documentary Studies student projects collection, 1980-2011 and undated RL.01266
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke, Spring 1987
  - Mintz, Louis Neil (Box 25)
    "The Carolina Theater and its Staff." Durham, N.C.
  - Owens, Nancy (Box 25)
    "Hill Street #6." Durham, N.C.
  - Rawlings, Tom C. (Box 25)
    "Oxford, North Carolina: People, Places, and Perspectives." Oxford, N.C.
  - Rogers, Smith (Box 25)
    "North Carolina State Museum of Natural Sciences." Raleigh, N.C.
  - Sackett, Carrie (Box 25)
    "The New World." Durham, N.C.
  - Stone, Margot (Box 25)
    "Hillhaven Rehabilitation and Convalescent Home." Durham, N.C.
  - Stroh, FraN.C.es (Box 25)
    "The Hare Krishna Commune." Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Walker, Jeff (Box 25)
    "Benson, North Carolina." Benson, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1987
  - Allen, Laura (Box 26)
    "Salvation is Free." Durham, N.C.
  - Bayer, Michael (Box 26)
    "The Durham Kennel Club." Durham, N.C.
  - Brown, Beverly M. (Box 26)
    "Jordan Lake." Durham, N.C.
  - Cathers, Courtney (Box 26)
    "Thoughts on Life at Hillcrest Convalescent Center in 1987." Durham, N.C.
  - Chinn, Jonathan (Box 26)
    "Portrait of an American Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Dick, Melissa A. (Box 26)
    "Immaculata Elementary School." Durham, N.C.
- UNC, Fall 1987
  - Cain, Chris (Box 27)
    "Trailer Parks." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Deifell, Tony (Box 27)
    "Markham's Chapel Baptist Church." Durham, N.C.
  - Forbes, Ellen G. (Box 27)
    "Photography at the Community School for People Under Six." Chapel Hill, N.C.
  - Kalow, Nancy (Box 27)
    "Under 21 and the After Hours: Teasing the Korean and their Fans." Durham/Raleigh/Chapel Hill, N.C.
  - MacKay, Kathleen (Box 27)
    "Agape Corner." Durham, N.C.
  - Shaughnessy, Maureen (Box 27)
    "Reverend Jerry Fisher - A Man, His Church, and His Family." Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Stoessl, Jeff (Box 27)
    "In Drewry." Drewry, N.C.
  - Gottsegen, FraN.C.ie (Box 27)
    "Cedar Terrace Trailer Park." Durham, N.C.
  - Guenther, Abigail (Box 27)
    "Middle Class Suburbia." Durham, N.C.
  - Stovall, Julie (Box 27)
    "Three Months with the Uhlenbergs." Chapel Hill, N.C.
- UNC, Fall 1987 and Duke, Spring 1988
  - Aherne, William E. III (Box 28)
    "The YMCA Daycare Center." Durham, N.C.
  - Araskog, Kathleen M. (Box 28)
    "Reflections on Time Spent on the Farm." location unknown
  - Bent, Stephen W. (Box 28)
    "The Hillside Hornets." Durham, N.C.
  - Bowen, Shelley A. (Box 28)
    "Where Do We Go From Here?" Durham, N.C.
  - Bridgers, Gray Carr (Box 28)
    "A Community of Farmers." Wilson, N.C.
  - Byer, Lisa K. (Box 28)
    "Eckerd's on Broad Street." Durham, N.C.
  - Carmichael, Trent A. (Box 28)
    "Passing Through the Underwoods." Orange County, N.C.
  - Hanley, Tara (Box 28)
    "Life at Fire Station 2, Durham, 1988." Durham, N.C.
  - Lattin, Tom (Box 28)
    "Station No. 1 - A Shift." Durham, N.C.
  - Massalon, Jennifer (Box 28)
    "Carolina Friends School." Orange County, N.C.
  - Millar, John P. (Box 29)
    "Perspectives on Ninth Street." Durham, N.C.
  - Pergament, Karina (Box 29)
    "Quail Roost Stables." Rougemont, N.C.
  - Petty, David Bruce (Box 29)
    "Edgemont." Durham, N.C.
  - Rodgers, Adam F. (Box 29)
    "A Vietnamese Family in North Carolina." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Salcedo, Eduardo A. (Box 29)
    "The Green Room: A Photographic Representation." Durham, N.C.
  - Tess, Elizabeth (Box 29)
    "Kids in the Neighborhood." Durham, N.C.
  - Thompson, Kimberly. (Box 29)
    "Neighborhood, Burch Avenue." Durham, N.C.
  - Vickers, Susan H. (Box 29)
    "Waiting to be Heard; Durham County Courthouse." Durham, N.C.
  - Whitington, H. Frances (Box 29)
    "A Different Culture." Tillery, N.C.
  - Wyman, Michael D. (Box 29)
    "Jo Jo Ex Mariner." location unknown
- Duke, Fall 1988 and UNC, Fall 1988
  - Bowen, Shelley A. (Box 30)
    "North Carolina School of Science and Math." Durham, N.C.
  - Cook, Cecily (Box 30)
    "Dega Community Series." Raleigh/Greensboro/Charlotte, N.C.
  - Feffer, Katie (Box 30)
    "Hall's Dairy." Orange County, N.C.
  - Freid, Bonnie (Box 30)
    "John Avery Boys Club." Durham, N.C.
  - Hoo, Jeffrey James (Box 30)
  - James, Cynthia T. (Box 30)
    "The Oxford Orphanage." Oxford, N.C.
  - Kehoe, Robb T. (Box 30)
    "The Inter-Faith Council Community Kitchen." Chapel Hill, N.C./ Carrboro, N.C.
  - Kehoe, Scott (Box 30)
    "Ruby and Wilbur." Carrboro, N.C.
  - McCain, Jodi-beth (Box 30)
    2215 Elder Street - Johnny and Bernadette's Home." Durham, N.C.
  - McFarlane, Camille (Box 30)
    "Greystone Baptist Church." Durham, N.C.
  - Paresky, Laura (Box 30)
    "American Communities: Durham Fire Station #2." Durham, N.C.
  - Spilker, Adam (Box 30)
    "Durham Fire Department Station 1: Shift A." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1989
  - Bader, Richard (Box 31)
    "Evelyn Jones and the Rest of 1109 Angier Street." Durham, N.C.
  - Bankston, Forrest (Box 31)
    "Watts Street Group Home for the Mentally Retarded." Durham, N.C.
  - Brown, Eric A. (Box 31)
    "American Communities." Bahama, N.C.
  - Callahan, Melissa (Box 31)
    "The Monks of St. John's House." Durham, N.C.
  - Drey, Laura (Box 31)
    "The Shiloh Community." Wake County, N.C.
  - Feingold, Lesley (Box 31)
    "Lakewood Avenue Children's School." Durham, N.C.
  - Fister, Wendy (Box 31)
  - Flores, Daniel (Box 31)
    "The Durham Community Kitchen." Durham, N.C.
  - Freundlich, James F. (Box 31)
    "The Durham Rest Home." Durham, N.C.
  - George, Charles R. (Box 31)
    "Life Flight Helicopter Program of Duke Hospital." Durham, N.C.
  - Goldstein, Jeffrey B. (Box 31)
    "The Duke School for Children." Durham, N.C.
  - Gupta, Vilma (Box 31)
  - Harris, Angela D. (Box 31)
    "The Growth of the Extended Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Higgins, Sally (Box 31)
    "Habitat for Humanity Home." Durham, N.C.
  - Karr, Catherine (Box 31)
    "The Cambanis Family." Chapel Hill, N.C.
  - Lavigne, Jill E. (Box 31)
    "Mary Milbourne and her Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Lublin, Kathy (Box 31)
    "The Greenwood Day Care Center." Durham, N.C.
  - McConchie, Scott (Box 31)
    "Calvin." Durham, N.C.
  - McKinnon, William B. III (Box 31)
    "Searching - A Photo Essay of the Durham Police Department." Durham, N.C.
  - McNamara, Mike (Box 31)
    "North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics." Durham, N.C.
  - Moller, Karen (Box 31)
    "Palmer's Grove Church." Durham, N.C.
  - Newsom, Andrew N. (Box 32)
    "Ms. Nellie Olive - Mid Way Service Station, Highway 49." Cedar Grove, N.C.
  - Ng, Judy (Box 32)
    "Lennox Baker Children's Hospital: Tammy McAdams." Durham, N.C.
  - Paresky, Laura (Box 32)
    "The Paytons." Durham, N.C.
  - Rosen, James (Box 32)
    "Fire Station No. 1 - Durham Fire Department." Durham, N.C.
  - Shackelford, Alison (Box 32)
    "A Home Away." Durham, N.C.
  - Tager, Suzanne (Box 32)
    "Bahá'i Faith." Location not identified; probably Durham.
  - Willemssen, Joseph (Box 32)
    "Lifestyle of Miura." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Spring 1990
  - Brown, Eric (Box 33)
    "The Bake Shop and C.I." Durham, N.C.
  - Nichols, Shay (Box 33)
    "Children in Transition." Durham, N.C. (?)
- Duke, Spring 1991
  - Blom, Elisabeth (Box 33)
    "My House." Durham, N.C.(?)
  - Burns, Clifford (Box 33)
    "Durham Fire Station 1." Durham, N.C.
  - Carlson, Dave (Box 33)
    "Treyburn, North Carolina." Treyburn, N.C.
  - Daniels, Libby (Box 33)
    "Trailer Park in Hillsborough." Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Falls, Laurel (Box 33)
    "Blood and Circumstances." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Hancock, Jeff (Box 33)
    "T.A. Grady." Durham, N.C.
  - Henigson, Jeffrey (Box 33)
    "HeadStart." Durham, N.C.
  - Jameson, Jennifer (Box 33)
    "Seventh Street Bar." Durham, N.C.
  - Joyce, Cynthia (Box 33)
    "East Campus Food Court." Durham, N.C.
  - Lublin, Kathi (Box 33)
    "American Snooker." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Mallory, Heather (Box 33)
    "Quail Roost Farm." Rougemont, N.C.
  - Martin, Wendy (Box 33)
    "The Dyer Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Moller, Karen (Box 33)
    "Los Trabajadores." Durham, N.C.
  - Stearn, Peter (Box 33)
    "The Ward Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Warren, Lisa Williams (Box 33)
    "Teen PregNancy." Durham, N.C.
  - Wasmer, Mark (Box 33)
    "Community Center for H.O.P.E." Durham, N.C.
  - Wilkiemeyer, Ann O'Hara Boswell (Box 33)
    "Egg Creams to Vanilla Cokes." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Spring 1992
  [See also oversize materials section for additional image for project on Durham barbershops, unidentified student.]
  - Allers, Jackson (Box 34)
    "Immigrant Workers." Location unknown.
  - Ashton, K.N. (Box 34)
    "Tobacco Road." [Durham, N.C.?]
  - Balfour, Valeria (Box 34)
    "Durham Cooperative School for Teenage Pregnant Girls." Durham, N.C.
  - Benetz, Beth Ann (Box 34)
    "Southern Sisters Bookstore." Durham, N.C.
  - Fiedler, Lee (Box 34)
    "Bus Stop." Durham, N.C.
  - Fisher, Kim (Box 34)
    "We are Everywhere." Durham, N.C.
  - Fuqua, Eleanor (Box 34)
    "Red Cross Bloodmobile." Durham, N.C.
  - Garrison, Julie (Box 34)
    "Bluefield Housing Project." Durham, N.C.
  - Goldstein Jeremy (Box 34)
    "The Young People's Performing Company." Durham, N.C.
  - Greit, Michelle (Box 34)
    "Kim Irwin, Performance Artist." Durham, N.C.
  - Harmon, John V. (Box 34)
    "The Durham Food Co-op." Durham, N.C.
  - Hendler, Noah (Box 34)
    "The Waterman Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Kuklinski, Alyce (Box 34)
    "St. John's House." Durham, N.C.
  - Mejia, Beatriz (Box 34)
    "Juanita's Kids." Durham, N.C.
  - Pottheiser, Jennifer (Box 34)
    "Durham Animal Shelter." Durham, N.C.
  - Rehmus, Scott (Box 34)
    "Ken Dawson." Carrboro/ Orange County, N.C.
  - Rimer, Wendy (Box 34)
    "Mexican Immigrant Family." Durham, N.C.
  - Salus, Danielle (Box 34)
  - Sanders, Jason (Box 34)
    "Waltz." Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Saunders, Sue (Box 34)
    "The Children's Community at Immaculate Conception." Durham, N.C.
  - Smegal, Betsy (Box 34)
    "WTVD Newsroom." Durham, N.C.
  - Stearn, Peter (Box 34)
    "New Hope Missionary Baptist Church." Chapel Hill, N.C.
  - Yu, Xiao (Box 34)
    "Sallie and Her World." Durham, N.C.
  - Oversize image by unidentified student from project entitled Durham Barber Shops (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Duke, Spring 1993
  - Adams, Bo (Box 35)
    "Emmanuel Church." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Anderson, Christina (Box 35)
    "The Spring 1993 Photography and Creative Writing Class at Parkwood Elementary." Durham, N.C.
  - Bernstein, Benjamin, 2 folders (Box 35)
    "Salvation Army." Durham, N.C.
  - Bianchi, Linda (Box 35)
  - Brown, Leslie (Box 35)
    "Crossroads." Durham, N.C.
  - DeHoratius, Ed (Box 35)
    "Equal but Separate - Race Relations at Duke." Durham, N.C.
  - Haughton, Peter (Box 35)
    "Durham County Animal Shelter." Durham, N.C.
  - Holroyd, Claire (Box 35)
    "Jessie Copeland and the Copeland Outreach Center." Raleigh, N.C.
  - Kelley, Sean (Box 35)
    "Cicada Summer: Anticipating Durham Station #5." Durham, N.C.
  - Pedersen, Ramona (Box 35)
  - Reefe, Donna (Box 35)
    "The White Star Laundromat." Durham, N.C.
  - Stout, Kristin (Box 35)
    "McDonalds' Drugstore." Durham, N.C.
  - VanDerWerf, Dade (Box 35)
    "The Duke University Transit System." Durham, N.C.
  - Wang, Alex (Box 35)
    "Orange Correctional Facility." Hillsborough, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1993
  - Poole, Laura (Box 35)
    "Life in the Fishtank." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Spring 1994
  - Ainsworth, Heather (Box 36)
    "Family and Community: Documenting a Personal History." Durham, and Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Bishop, Laura (Box 36)
    "Habitat for Humanity." Durham, N.C.
  - Brown, Joshua (Box 36)
    "Observation in Progress - Duke Primate Center." Durham, N.C.
  - Cirillo, Karen (Box 36)
    "The Community Kitchen." Durham, N.C.
  - DeVito, Dave (Box 36)
    "Personal Statement - Duke Laundry Service." Durham, N.C.
  - Dominguez, Jennifer (Box 36)
    "Satisfaction's Restaurant and Bar." Durham, N.C.
  - Dunfee, Jennifer (Box 36)
    "Amanda." Durham, N.C.
  - Friedlander, Peter Eric (Box 36)
    "King's Barber Shop." Durham, N.C.
  - Greitens, Eric R. (Box 36)
    "The Durham Boxing Gym." Durham, N.C.
  - Gruendler, Shelley (Box 36)
    "The Raleigh Farmers Market." Raleigh, N.C.
  - Kardon, Gabrielle (Box 36)
    "Chicken Farming: At Work with Jane and Teresa." Chatham County, N.C.
  - Kirkpatrick, Robin (Box 36)
    "Athletes of the YMCA." Durham, N.C.
  - Lail, Shannon (Box 37)
    "Behind the Scenes." Durham, N.C.
  - Laufenberg, Jeffrey S. (Box 37)
    "The Faces of the Starlite." Durham, N.C.
  - Light, Andrew (Box 37)
    "Bullock's Barbeque." Durham, N.C.
  - Lynn, Doug (Box 37)
    "ACRA." Durham, N.C.
  - Maggio, Shannon (Box 37)
    "State Farmer's Market." Raleigh, N.C.
  - Monroe, Bill (Box 37)
    "The Tackle Shop, Inc." Durham, N.C.
  - Rechberger, Kristin (Box 37)
    "The Green Room." Durham, N.C.
  - Sakowitz, Jo-Ellyn (Box 37)
    "The Quail Roost Community." Rougemont, N.C.
  - Schulman, Wendy (Box 37)
    "Chiquita." Durham, N.C.
  - Shields, Amy (Box 37)
    "Bruegger's Bagel Bakery." Durham, N.C.
  - Sims, Christopher (Box 37)
    "Spectrum House." Durham, N.C.
  - Stein, Robin (Box 37)
    "Honey's Restaurant." Durham, N.C.
  - Wiesner, Catherine (Box 37)
    "Energy and Love." Durham, N.C.
  - Womble, Matt (Box 37)
    "Saddle Soar." [Location unknown; may be Quail Roost equestrian community, north of Durham, N.C.]
- Duke, Fall 1994
  - Bronner, Jamie (Box 38)
    "Oval Drive Park." Durham, N.C.
  - Caminos, Josephine (Box 38)
    "Welcome to McDonald's Drug Store, Inc." Durham, N.C.
  - Crespo, Joseph (Box 38)
    "The Duke Cross Country Team." Durham, N.C.
  - Donner, Andrew (Box 38)
    "A Photographic Analysis of Laundromat Patrons." Durham, N.C.
  - Goldberg, Heather (Box 38)
    "Volunteers for Youth." Durham, N.C.
  - Kravis, Robert (Box 38)
    "Mrs. Lord's Third Grade." Durham, N.C.
  - Lee, Anna (Box 38)
  - Litz, Courtney (Box 38)
    "Oakhaven Retirement Center." Durham, N.C.
  - Nasrallah, Caroline (Box 38)
    "Ligget and Meyers, Inc.." Durham, N.C.
  - Sher, Rachel (Box 38)
    "The Durham County Judicial Building." Durham, N.C.
  - Young, Kimberly C. (Box 38)
    "My Life: A Portrait of a Young Girl." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Spring 1995
  - Litz, Courtney (Box 39)
    "K-Mart." Durham, N.C.
  - Moore, Victoria (Box 39)
    "Kroger Store." Durham, N.C.
  - Pasternak, Katherine (Box 39)
    "Inkslingers Tattoo and Body Piercing." Durham, N.C.
  - Patel, Shetali (Box 39)
    "Home for the Mentally Disabled." [Durham, N.C.?]
  - Piech, William (Box 39)
    "Working at the Rathskeller." Durham, N.C.
  - Seybolt, Heather (Box 39)
    "A. G. Gregory, Police Officer." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1995
  - Bianchi, Danielle (Box 39)
    "Meet Me at Sunset...And Bring Your Dog, Too." Durham, N.C.
  - Breschiani, Alessandra (Box 39)
    "The Veteran's Affairs Medical Center." Durham, N.C.
  - Glenn, Ben (Box 39)
    "A Better Light, A Greater Joy." Chapel Hill/Durham, N.C.
  - Goodrich, Catherine (Box 39)
    "Valley Run." Durham, N.C.
  - Hardy, Tom (Box 39)
    "Best Buddies." Durham, N.C.
  - Hauser, Megan (Box 39)
    "Epworth Dormitory." Durham, N.C.
  - Lyttle, Kristin (Box 39)
    "Captured Stories." Cary, N.C.
  - McMahon, Connette P. (Box 39)
    "The Morgans." Durham, N.C.
  - Pincus, David (Box 40)
    "Field's Laundromat." Durham, N.C.
  - Rathod, Rahul (Box 40)
    "Kindergarten." Durham, N.C. (?)
  - Robell, Laura (Box 40)
    "Durham Service Corps." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Rose, Megan (Box 40)
    "Methodist Retirement Community." Durham, N.C.
  - Rosen, Jamie (Box 40)
    "The Community Center for H.O.P.E." Durham, N.C.
  - Salsbury, Jessica (Box 40)
    "Personalities: Durham Fire Department Station Two." Durham, N.C.
  - Smith, Logan (Box 40)
    "S.E.E.D.S." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Spring 1996
  - McMahon, Connette P. (Box 40)
    "The Nicholsons and Lamberths." Durham, N.C.
  - Quinn, Michele (Box 40)
    "Family Life." Location unknown.
  - Robell, Laura (Box 40)
    "Women of Durham." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Rosen, Jamie (Box 40)
    "Walltown." Durham, N.C.
  - Scotnicki (Box 40)
    "Carolina Sky Sports." Louisburg, N.C.
  - Smith, Jaclae (Box 40)
    "Black Men in Academia." Chapel Hill/Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1996
  - Charlebois, Nicole (Box 41)
    "Lenox Baker Children's Hospital." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Giordono, Joe (Box 41)
    "Fire Station #1." Durham, N.C.
  - Heyman, Alex (Box 41)
    "Ligget and Meullers Tobacco Co." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.]
  - Hutchinson, Shawn (Box 41)
    "Women's Center." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Johnson, Chris (Box 41)
    "The Galvan Family." Chapel Hill, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Khan, Michelle (Box 41)
    "Department of Surgery."Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Oishi, A. Christopher (Box 41)
    "On Photographing Dogs." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Rachapudi, Sumita (Box 41)
    "Hospital."[Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Robinette, Catherine (Box 41)
    "Durham Fire Department." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Shapiro, Nina (Box 41)
    "Zach." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Tosh, Susan (Box 41)
    "Caring House." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - VanBerg, Jill (Box 41)
    "Sustenance Farm." Bear Creek, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Wu, Gregory (Box 41)
    Children's Hospital, Durham [?], N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Spring 1997
  - Cubillos, Ingrid (Box 42)
    "Duke Children's Hospital Playrooms - 4th floor." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Dean, Mason (Box 42)
    Middle Eastern Communities. Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - DeNoyer, Annette (Box 42)
    "Washington Duke Golf Course and Trail." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Golden, Becca (Box 42)
    "East Campus Weight Room." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Grant, Kelly (Box 42)
    [Duke Hospital?]. Slide format only.
  - Hurty, Charles (Box 42)
    "Colony Park Animal Hospital." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Harkrader, Brooke (Box 42)
    "Smokers at Duke." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Machanda, Sean (Box 42)
    College Radio Station]Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Mischley, Joy Barber (Box 42)
    "La tienda de Don Jose." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Mitchell, Gregory (Box 42)
    Duke Sports Medicine. Slide format only.
  - Parbhu, Keshini (Box 42)
    Retirement home. Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Robinette, Catherine (Box 42)
    "Julie and Kalsea, Tonya and Asia." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Shapiro, Nina (Box 42)
    "Stage 1." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Son, Heejung Heidi (Box 42)
    "The Mad Hatter's Bake Shop." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Sherman, Jane (Box 43)
    "Kindergarten." [Durham, N.C.?]
  - van Berg, Jill (Box 43)
    "The Silk Road Teahouse." Chapel Hill, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Williams, Colin (Box 43)
    "Oxford Orphanage." Oxford, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Wu, David (Box 43)
    "For the Love of Music." Durham, N.C.
  - Wu, Greg (Box 43)
    "Children's Hospital." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Yellin, Anna (Box 43)
    "View in the Canopy." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1997
  - Baron, Rhea (Box 43)
    "The Town of Hillsborough." Hillsborough, N.C.
  - Brooks, Amanda (Box 43)
    "Midwife, Smidwife." Chapel Hill, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Carter, Cason (Box 43)
    "Growing Up in Agape." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Chang, Victor (Box 44)
    "Methodist Retirement Community." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Eggebeen, Rachel (Box 44)
    "Homeschooling." Raleigh, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Ermentrout, Dania (Box 44)
    "Duke South Hospital." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Gharson, Brandon (Box 44)
    "Habitat for Humanity." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Gottesman, Eric (Box 44)
    "McDonald's Drug Store and Dogstar Tattoo Company." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Lee, Olivia (Box 44)
    "Everyday People." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Haurtman, Stephen (Box 44)
    "Raleigh Durham International Airport." Raleigh, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Levy, Marcy (Box 44)
    "The Opportunity Place." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Littlefield, Brandie (Box 44)
    "Young People's Performing Company." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Lovell, Lesley (Box 44)
    "Triangle Residential Options for Substance Abusers." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Moore, Tracie (Box 44)
    Afterschool program? Location unknown
  - Nadell, Neeli (Box 44)
    "Living with Leukemia: The Stories of Katie and Ben." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Pressley, Kimberly (Box 44)
    "Durham Interfaith Hospitality Network." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Reefe, Katie (Box 44)
    "Construction Project." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
  - Smith, Heather (Box 44)
    "Jóvenes Lideres en Acción." Durham, N.C.
  - Trask, Claire (Box 44)
    Franklin Street] [Chapel Hill, N.C.
  - Miscellaneous (Box 44)
- Duke, Spring 1998
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
  - Emanuel, Ryan (Box 45)
    "My Family, My People." Pembroke, N.C. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Dresner, Jeremy (Box 45)
    "John Avery Boys and Girls Club." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Harkinson, Josh (Box 45)
    "Tony, Steve, and John." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Marcello, Kerci (Box 45)
    "On the Courts." Durham, N.C. Slide format only. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Moore, Traci (Box 45)
    "Life in Transition." Durham, N.C. Slides in addition to prints.
  - Pazden, Michele (Box 45)
    "Duke Barber Shop." Durham, N.C. Slide format only. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Piggie, Stefanie (Box 45)
    "Chewning Middle School." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Fall 1998
  - Forrest, Jessica (Box 45)
    "The ISKON Community at New Goloka." Hillsborough, N.C. Slide format only.
  - King, Leslie (Box 45)
    "The Formation of a New Community: Kestrel Heights Charter School." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Spring 1999
  - Hindman, Vince (Box 45)
    "Ain't Misbehavin'." Durham, N.C. Slide format only. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Hyde, Katie (Box 45)
    "Latino and Latina Immigrants in North Carolina." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Mutchler, Colin (Box 45)
    "Sides of Justice: our Subtle Civil War." Durham, N.C. Slide format only.
  - Richie, Brooke (Box 46)
    "Roxboro." Roxboro, N.C. Slide format only. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Snowden, Kelly (Box 46)
    "Oh, Very Young." Location unknown. Slide format only. Audio cassette enclosed.
  - Stowell, Jesse (Box 46)
    "Seeds." Durham, N.C.
- Duke, Fall 1999
  - Rooks, Christopher (Box 46)
    "Carrboro Farmer's Market." Carrboro, N.C. Slide format only.
- Duke, Fall 2000
  - Larsen, Erica (Box 62)
    "Quail Roost in Photos." (Essay)
  - Larsen, Erica, 2 prints (Box 66)
    "Quail Roost in Photos." Black-and-white prints are in window mats.
  - Larsen, Erica, 2 albums (Box 67)
    "Quail Roost in Photos."
  - Maggio, Justin (Box 62)
    "Photographing the AMF Lanes." Black-and-white prints.
  - Thomas, Simmons (Box 62)
    "Reflections on Project"
- Duke, Spring 2001
  - Callazo, Erin (Box 46)
    "Agape Corner." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Reitz, Jessica (Box 46)
    "Walltown." Location unknown. Slide format only.
  - Wilson, Lucy (Box 46)
    "Olufolabi Family." [Durham, N.C.?]. Slide format only.
- Duke, Fall 2001
  - Duke, HIST 195S, The Coastal South, Fall 2001, 1 box